{
    "subject": "resource/Charles_Durning",
    "predicate": "property/placeOfDeath",
    "object": "resource/Manhattan",
    "human_readable": "Charles Durning died in Manhattan.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9100930690765381,
            "question": "Where did Charles Durning die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8914375305175781,
            "question": "Did Charles Durning live in Manhattan before his death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8360563516616821,
            "question": "When did Charles Durning die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8239433765411377,
            "question": "Were there any notable events happening in Manhattan around the time of Charles Durning's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6923392415046692,
            "question": "What was the cause of Charles Durning's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3817267119884491,
            "question": "Was Charles Durning an actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3068237602710724,
            "question": "Who were some of Charles Durning's contemporaries?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28880825638771057,
            "question": "What was Charles Durning's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19789667427539825,
            "question": "What were some of Charles Durning's famous roles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.14011020958423615,
            "question": "What is Manhattan known for?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Charles Durning died in Manhattan.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5359_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What were some of Charles Durning's famous roles?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5359_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was Charles Durning's profession?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5359_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who were some of Charles Durning's contemporaries?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5359_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5359_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5359_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5359_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5359_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5359_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5359_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5359_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5359_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5359_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5359_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the requested format:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nThis is because all of the documents mention that Charles Durning passed away or died, and many of them specify that he died in his Manhattan home at the age of 89. Therefore, the statement \"Charles Durning died in Manhattan\" is supported by the information in the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple mentions that Charles Durning passed away at his home in Manhattan, New York. Therefore, the statement \"Charles Durning died in Manhattan\" is supported by the given information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}